A Guide to Dr. Vamik D. Volkan Papers
Claude Moore Health Sciences Library
- Vamik Volkan Papers - Estonia Project: Final Report on Ethnic Reconcilation in Estonia(November 1996 - June 1999), 1999(8/15), TD (Box-folder 013:016)
- Vamik Volkan Papers - Estonia Project: Letter from Endel Talvik, 1999(10/20), TD (Box-folder 013:017)
- Vamik Volkan Papers - Estonia Project: Letter to Peter Vinkelis, 1999(12/20), TD (Box-folder 013:018)
- Vamik Volkan Papers - Estonia Project: Photos of Trip to Estonia, 1999, Photo Album (Box-folder 013:019)
- Vamik Volkan Papers - Estonia Project: Letter from Jane R. Boissevain, 2000(2/8), TD (Box-folder 013:020)
- Vamik Volkan Papers - Estonia Project: Letter to Vaira Vike-Freiberga, 2000(5/31), TD (Box-folder 013:021)
- Vamik Volkan Papers - Estonia Project: Invitation Letter to the Fourth Baltic Congress of Psychology, 2000(5/31), TD (Box-folder 013:022)
  Letter, Report
- Vamik Volkan Papers - Estonia Project: Letter to Minister Valdis Birkavs, 2000(6/5), TD (Box-folder 013:023)
- Vamik Volkan Papers - Estonia Project: Letter from Juris G. Draguns, 2000(6/5), TD (Box-folder 013:024)
- Vamik Volkan Papers - Estonia Project: Letter from Allan King, 2001(5/25), TD (Box-folder 013:025)
- Vamik Volkan Papers - Estonia Project: Map of Tallinn, Estonia, ND, map (Box-folder 013:026)
- Vamik Volkan Papers - Estonia Project: Tree Model - Estonia, ND, TD (Box-folder 013:027)
  Pictures
- Vamik Volkan Papers - Carter Center: State of World Conflict Report, 1991-1992, 1991-1992, Report Book (Box-folder 013:028)
- Vamik Volkan Papers - Carter Center: Volkan's Letter to the Cneter, 1991(3/12), TD (Box-folder 013:029)
- Vamik Volkan Papers - Carter Center: Letter from the Center, 1991(7/16), TD (Box-folder 013:030)
  Letter, Newspaper Articles
- Vamik Volkan Papers - Carter Center: Volkan's Letter to the Center, 1991(9/30), TD (Box-folder 013:031)
- Vamik Volkan Papers - Carter Center: Letter from the Center, 1991(10/22), TD (Box-folder 013:032)
- Vamik Volkan Papers - Carter Center: INN Consultation Participants List, 1992(1/11), TD (Box-folder 013:033)
- Vamik Volkan Papers - Carter Center: Report on "Redefining Our Approach to Ethnic Conflicts", 1992(1/15-16), TD (Box-folder 013:034)
- Vamik Volkan Papers - Carter Center: Letter from the Center, 1992(6/11), TD (Box-folder 013:035)
- Vamik Volkan Papers - Carter Center: Memorandum on INN Core Group Retreat, 1992(10/19), TD (Box-folder 013:036)
- Vamik Volkan Papers - Carter Center: INN Report of Activities, February - August 1993, 1993(2-8), TD (Box-folder 013:037)
- Vamik Volkan Papers - Carter Center: Letter from the Center, 1993(2/23), TD (Box-folder 013:038)
- Vamik Volkan Papers - Carter Center: CSMHI Information of the New INN Publication, 1993(12/7), TD (Box-folder 013:039)
- Vamik Volkan Papers - Carter Center: Volkan's Letter to the Center, 1994(7/5), TD (Box-folder 013:040)
- Vamik Volkan Papers - Carter Center: Letter from the Center, 1994(10/1), TD (Box-folder 013:041)
- Vamik Volkan Papers - Carter Center: State of World Conflict Report of 1994-1995, 1994-1995, Report Book (Box-folder 013:042)
- Vamik Volkan Papers - Carter Center: Letter from the Center, 1995(6/23), TD (Box-folder 013:043)
- Vamik Volkan Papers - Carter Center: INN Quarterly Update of Activities, July 1995, 1995(8), TD (Box-folder 013:044)
- Vamik Volkan Papers - Carter Center: Letter from the Center, 1995(8/16), TD (Box-folder 013:045)
- Vamik Volkan Papers - Carter Center: Proposal for INN-Sponsored Project, 1997(3/25), TD (Box-folder 013:046)
- Vamik Volkan Papers - Carter Center: Volkan's Letter to President Carter, 1997(5/1), TD (Box-folder 013:047)
- Vamik Volkan Papers - Carter Center: Volkan's Letter to James Bill, 1997(6/23), TD (Box-folder 013:048)
- Vamik Volkan Papers - Carter Center: Letter from the Center, 1997(11/5), TD (Box-folder 013:049)
- Vamik Volkan Papers - Carter Center: Press Release about Albanian National Development Strategy, 1998(2/13), TD (Box-folder 014:001)
  News Release
- Vamik Volkan Papers - Carter Center: Volkan's Letter to the Center (Subject: USAID Greater Horn of Africa Project- Conflict Resolution Aspects), 1998(3/12), TD (Box-folder 014:002)
- Vamik Volkan Papers - Carter Center: Job Announcement for the Director of Conflict Resolution Program, 1998(4/2), TD (Box-folder 014:003)
- Vamik Volkan Papers - Carter Center: Estonia Report, 1998(8/13), TD, Pamphlet (Box-folder 014:004)
- Vamik Volkan Papers - Carter Center: Letter of Mikhail Gorbachev to President Carter, ND, TD (Box-folder 014:005)
- Vamik Volkan Papers - Carter Center: Museum of the Jimmy Carter Library, ND, Brochure (Box-folder 014:006)
- Vamik Volkan Papers - Carter Center: Volkan's Photo, ND, Photocopies Photo (Box-folder 014:007)
- Vamik Volkan Papers - Kuwait Project: Memorandum on the Fringe Benefit Rates for 1992-93 and Beyond, 1992(2/17), TD (Box-folder 014:008)
- Vamik Volkan Papers - Kuwait Project: Howell's Report, "Tragedy, Trauma... amd Triumph: Reclaiming Integrity and Initiative from Victimization", 1993(1/29), TD (Box-folder 014:009)
- Vamik Volkan Papers - Kuwait Project: Seminar in Kuwait, 1993(3/5-8), TD (Box-folder 014:010)
- Vamik Volkan Papers - Kuwait Project: Letter to Dr. Basher S. Al-Rashidi, 1993(3/16), TD (Box-folder 014:011)
- Vamik Volkan Papers - Kuwait Project: Letter to Dr. Adnan Al-Shatti, 1993(3/31), TD (Box-folder 014:012)
- Vamik Volkan Papers - Kuwait Project: Proposal for the Office of Social Development at Amiri Diwan, 1993(4/16), TD (Box-folder 014:013)
- Vamik Volkan Papers - Kuwait Project: Letter from Ahmed Al-Shatti, 1993(4/21), TD (Box-folder 014:014)
  Report, Letter
- Vamik Volkan Papers - Kuwait Project: Howell-Ahmed Al-Shatti Correspondence [Subject: International Seminars on the Effect of the Iraqu Invasion on Kuwait], 1993(3/20-4/21), TD (Box-folder 014:015)
- Vamik Volkan Papers - Kuwait Project: Letter from Ahmed Al-Shatti, 1993(4/24), TD (Box-folder 014:016)
- Vamik Volkan Papers - Kuwait Project: Letter to Ahmed Al-Shatti, 1993(5/3), TD (Box-folder 014:017)
- Vamik Volkan Papers - Kuwait Project: A Proposal for Establishing a Kuwait Center, 1993(5/10), TD (Box-folder 014:018)
- Vamik Volkan Papers - Kuwait Project: A Proposal for SDO/CSMHI Cooperation, 1993(5/11), TD (Box-folder 014:019)
- Vamik Volkan Papers - Kuwait Project: Letter to Abdall, 1993(5/20), AD (Box-folder 014:020)
- Vamik Volkan Papers - Kuwait Project: Letter to Ahmed Al-Shatti, 1993(5/25), TD (Box-folder 014:021)
- Vamik Volkan Papers - Kuwait Project: Howell-Fahad Correspondence [Subject: Invitation to the International Conference on the Effect of the Iraqi Invasion on Kuwait], 1993(6/7-8), TD (Box-folder 014:022)
- Vamik Volkan Papers - Kuwait Project: Howell-Fahad Correspondence [subject: SDO/CSMHI Consultations in Kuwait], 1993(6/12-23), TD (Box-folder 014:023)
- Vamik Volkan Papers - Kuwait Project: Agreement Terms between SDO and CSMHI, 1993(6/29), TD (Box-folder 014:024)
- Vamik Volkan Papers - Kuwait Project: CSMHI Draft Work Program and Project Budget, 1993(7)-1994(6), TD (Box-folder 014:025)
- Vamik Volkan Papers - Kuwait Project: Letter to Mohamad Al-Rumaihi, 1993(7/5), TD (Box-folder 014:026)
- Vamik Volkan Papers - Kuwait Project: Letter to Basheer Al-Rashdi and Hasan Makki, 1993(7/11), TD (Box-folder 014:027)
- Vamik Volkan Papers - Kuwait Project: Letter from Don E. Detmer, 1993(7/23), TD (Box-folder 014:028)
- Vamik Volkan Papers - Kuwait Project: Proposal Approval Sheet, 1993(7/29), TD (Box-folder 014:029)
- Vamik Volkan Papers - Kuwait Project: Correspondence [Subject: SDO-CSMHI Project], 1993(8/9-17), TD (Box-folder 014:030)
- Vamik Volkan Papers - Kuwait Project: Howell-Vaught Correspondence [Subject: Conflict Management Programs], 1993(8/24-26), TD (Box-folder 014:031)
- Vamik Volkan Papers - Kuwait Project: Howell-Fahed Correspondence [Subject: September Visit to Kuwait], 1993(8/26-9/16), TD (Box-folder 014:032)
- Vamik Volkan Papers - Kuwait Project: Itinerary of September Visit to Kuwait, 1993(9/21-26), TD (Box-folder 014:033)
- Vamik Volkan Papers - Kuwait Project: Newsletter Article, "CSMHI to Undertake Project in Kuwait", 1993(10/1), Newsletter (Box-folder 014:034)
- Vamik Volkan Papers - Kuwait Project: 1993(10/2), TD (Box-folder 014:035)
- Vamik Volkan Papers - Kuwait Project: CSMHI Office Memorandum [Subject: Middle East Research], 1993(10/7), TD (Box-folder 014:036)
- Vamik Volkan Papers - Kuwait Project: Howell-Nafisi Correspondence, 1993(10/10), AD (Box-folder 014:037)
- Vamik Volkan Papers - Kuwait Project: Letter to Fahad [Subject: November Visit to SDO Counterparts], 1993(10/10), TD (Box-folder 014:038)
- Vamik Volkan Papers - Kuwait Project: Howell-Makki Correspondence [Subject: November Visit to US], 1993(10/12-14), TD (Box-folder 014:039)
- Vamik Volkan Papers - Kuwait Project: Letter to Gerry Kane, 1993(10/18), TD (Box-folder 014:040)
- Vamik Volkan Papers - Kuwait Project: Howell-Mohamad Al-Rumaihi Correspondence, 1993(10/18-20), TD (Box-folder 014:041)
- Vamik Volkan Papers - Kuwait Project: Letter to Fahad Al-Naser, 1993(10/20), TD (Box-folder 014:042)
- Vamik Volkan Papers - Kuwait Project: Office of Sponsored programs Notice of Award, 1993(10/20-25), TD (Box-folder 014:043)
- Vamik Volkan Papers - Kuwait Project: Howell-Gerry Kane Correspondence [Subject: First Payment], 1993(10/23), TD (Box-folder 014:044)
- Vamik Volkan Papers - Kuwait Project: Howell-Nafisi Correspondence, 1993(10/27), AD (Box-folder 014:045)
- Vamik Volkan Papers - Kuwait Project: Howell-Katherine Kenny Correspondence, 1993(10/27-31), TD (Box-folder 014:046)
- Vamik Volkan Papers - Kuwait Project: First 30 Percent Payment, 1993(11/1), TD (Box-folder 014:047)
- Vamik Volkan Papers - Kuwait Project: Howell-Hasan Makki Ibrahim Correspondence, 1993(11/1-3), TD (Box-folder 014:048)
- Vamik Volkan Papers - Kuwait Project: CSMHI Advisory Board Meeting Minutes, 1993(11/19), TD (Box-folder 014:049)
  Minutes
- Vamik Volkan Papers - Kuwait Project: Schedule of Drs. Hasan Makki Ibrahim and Ahmad Al-Mayyal's Visit to CSMHI, 1993(11/14-19), TD (Box-folder 014:050)
  Letter, Memorandum
- Vamik Volkan Papers - Kuwait Project: Participation of Dr. Greg Saathoff in the CSMHI Field Trip to Kuwait, 1993(11/22-23), TD (Box-folder 014:051)
- Vamik Volkan Papers - Kuwait Project: CSMHI Field Trip to Kuwait, 1993(12/4-12), TD (Box-folder 014:052)
  Letter, Photocopies of Passports
- Vamik Volkan Papers - Kuwait Project: Appointment of Scott Harrop for the Position Research Assistant for the Kuwait Project, 1993(12/12), TD (Box-folder 014:053)
- Vamik Volkan Papers - Kuwait Project: New Year's Greeting to SDO, 1993(12/29), TD (Box-folder 014:054)
- Vamik Volkan Papers - Kuwait Project: Second Payment, 1993(12/30), TD (Box-folder 014:055)
- Vamik Volkan Papers - Kuwait Project: Notice of Award Correction 1994(1/14), TD (Box-folder 014:056)
- Vamik Volkan Papers - Kuwait Project: J. Anderson Thomson, Jr.'s Draft, "Kuwait: A Post Traumatic State", 1994(1/7), TD (Box-folder 014:057)
- Vamik Volkan Papers - Kuwait Project: J. Anderson Thomson, Jr.'s Draft, "Diwanneah", 1994(1/7), TD (Box-folder 014:058)
- Vamik Volkan Papers - Kuwait Project: J. Anderson Thomson, Jr.'s Draft, "Individual Cases", 1994(1/7), TD (Box-folder 014:059)
- Vamik Volkan Papers - Kuwait Project: Notice of Award and Budget Amendment, 1994(2/24), TD (Box-folder 014:060)
- Vamik Volkan Papers - Kuwait Project: Letter from Hasan Makki Ibrahim, 1994(3/8), TD (Box-folder 014:061)
- Vamik Volkan Papers - Kuwait Project: Interim Report, 1994(3/30), TD (Box-folder 014:062)
- Vamik Volkan Papers - Kuwait Project: Letter from Hasan Makki Ibrahim [Subject: Proposed TV Documentary], 1994(4/13), TD (Box-folder 014:063)
- Vamik Volkan Papers - Kuwait Project: Account Report, August 1993-June 1994, 1994(4/18), TD (Box-folder 014:064)
- Vamik Volkan Papers - Kuwait Project: Letter from Hasan Makki Ibrahim [Subject: Interim Report], 1994(5/12), TD (Box-folder 014:065)
- Vamik Volkan Papers - Kuwait Project: Notice of Award and Budget Amendement, 1994(7/8), TD (Box-folder 014:066)
- Vamik Volkan Papers - Kuwait Project: Account Report, August 1993-October 1994, 1994(7/12), TD, AD (Box-folder 014:067)
  Report, Memo
- Vamik Volkan Papers - Kuwait Project: Letter from SDO Kuwait [Subject: Passport], 1994(8/1), AD (Box-folder 014:068)
- Vamik Volkan Papers - Kuwait Project: Howell-Judith L. White Correspondence, 1994(10/4-8), TD (Box-folder 014:069)
- Vamik Volkan Papers - Kuwait Project: Letter to Hasan Makki Ibrahim,, 1994(10/10), TD (Box-folder 014:070)
- Vamik Volkan Papers - Kuwait Project: Magazine Article, "Building Bridges to the Gulf", 1995(Spring), Magazine Article (Box-folder 014:071)
- Vamik Volkan Papers - Kuwait Project: Newspaper Article, "Reunion Recalls Days at Embassy in Kuwait" 1995(8/7), Newspaper Article (Box-folder 014:072)
- Vamik Volkan Papers - Kuwait Project: Magazine Article, 1995(10/26), Magazine Article (Box-folder 014:073)
- Vamik Volkan Papers - Kuwait Project: Newspaper Article, "Project Completed, Ambassador Makes Journey Back to Kuwait", 1995(11/28), Newspaper Article (Box-folder 014:074)
- Vamik Volkan Papers - Kuwait Project: Newspaper Article, "US, Kuwait Ties to be Boosted", 1995(12/5), Newspaper Article (Box-folder 014:075)
- Vamik Volkan Papers - Kuwait Project: N.D., AD, Federal Express Receipt (Box-folder 014:076)
- Vamik Volkan Papers - Georgia Project: Meeting with Georgian Foreign Minister, 1991(5/30), TD (Box-folder 015:001)
- Vamik Volkan Papers - Georgia Project: List of CSMHI Members Visiting Georgia in Fall, 1994, 1991(7/9), TD (Box-folder 015:002)
- Vamik Volkan Papers - Georgia Project: Correspondence with Georgian Embassy [Subject: Trip to Georgia], 1991(9/11-10/1), TD (Box-folder 015:003)
- Vamik Volkan Papers - Georgia Project: CSMHI Grand Proposal for Fall 1992, 1992(9/28), TD (Box-folder 015:004)
- Vamik Volkan Papers - Georgia Project: Volkan-Tedo Japaridze Correspondence [Subject: Japaridze's Visit to CSMHI], 1995(10/10-13), TD (Box-folder 015:005)
- Vamik Volkan Papers - Georgia Project: Letter to Japaridze, 1996(5/29), TD (Box-folder 015:006)
- Vamik Volkan Papers - Georgia Project: Report "Psycho-Social Rehabilitation of IDPs in Georgia", 1997, TD (Box-folder 015:007)
- Vamik Volkan Papers - Georgia Project: Report of the IREX Forum: "Traumatized Societies: Ethnic Conflict in Georgia", 1997(12/2), TD (Box-folder 015:008)
  Brochure
- Vamik Volkan Papers - Georgia Project: Invitation from the President of Georgia, 1998, TD (Box-folder 015:009)
- Vamik Volkan Papers - Georgia Project: Pocket Guide Book for Pourists [Welcome to Georgia], 1998, TD (Box-folder 015:010)
  Tourist Book
- Vamik Volkan Papers - Georgia Project: The 80th Anniversary of the Declaration of Georgian Independence, 1998(5/19), Booklet (Box-folder 015:011)
- Vamik Volkan Papers - Georgia Project: Grant Proposal, "Reducing Transgenerational Transmission of Ethinic Conflict", 1998(7), TD (Box-folder 015:012)
- Vamik Volkan Papers - Georgia Project: Letter from Avtandil Jorbendze [Subject: Minister of Health of Georgia], 1999(3/30), TD (Box-folder 015:013)
- Vamik Volkan Papers - Georgia Project: Scientific-Practical Conference - Volkan's Leucture, "The Concept of 'Deposited Image' and Transgenerational Transmission", 1999(8/9), TD (Box-folder 015:014)
- Vamik Volkan Papers - Georgia Project: Newspaper Article, 1999(8/18-24), newspaper Article (Box-folder 015:015)
- Vamik Volkan Papers - Georgia Project: Grant Proposal, "Helping the Helpers - Experimental Training for Georgian and South Ossetian Aid Workers", 1999(10), TD (Box-folder 015:016)
- Vamik Volkan Papers - Georgia Project: Final Report of September 1998 to August 1999, "Reducing Transgenerational Transmission of Ethnic Conflict", 1999(10), TD (Box-folder 015:017)
- Vamik Volkan Papers - Georgia Project: Newspaper Article, 1999, Newspaper Article (Box-folder 015:018)
- Vamik Volkan Papers - Georgia Project: Volkan-Nelson Correspondence [Subject: Grant Offer], 2000(1/28-29), TD (Box-folder 015:019)
- Vamik Volkan Papers - Georgia Project: First Interim Report, June 2000 - November 2000, 2000(12/1), TD (Box-folder 015:020)
- Vamik Volkan Papers - Georgia Project: Georgia-South Ossetian Workshop Report, 2000(3/11-12), TD (Box-folder 015:021)
- Vamik Volkan Papers - Georgia Project: Second Interim Report, December 2000 - March 2001, 2001(4/1), TD (Box-folder 015:022)
- Vamik Volkan Papers - Georgia Project: USIP Grant, 2001(6/22), TD, AD (Box-folder 015:023)
- Vamik Volkan Papers - Georgia Project: Financial Report for the Helping the Helpers Experimental Training, 2001(7/5), TD (Box-folder 015:024)
- Vamik Volkan Papers - Georgia Project: Letter to Embassador Tedo Japaridze, 2001(8/13), TD (Box-folder 015:025)
- Vamik Volkan Papers - Georgia Project: Letter from Judy Barsalou [Subject: USIP Grant], 2001(8/16), TD (Box-folder 015:026)
- Vamik Volkan Papers - Georgia Project: Final Report, June 2000 - May 2001, 2001(8/31), TD (Box-folder 015:027)
- Vamik Volkan Papers - Georgia Project: Speak of Georgian Embassador About September 11, 2001(11/30), TD (Box-folder 015:028)
  Lecture Announcement, Newspaper
- Vamik Volkan Papers - Georgia Project: Report on the International Research Center for East-west Relationships in Georgia, 2001(12/10), TD (Box-folder 015:029)
- Vamik Volkan Papers - Georgia Project: Narrative Report on FDHR Projects, 2001-2002, 2001-2002, TD, Pamphlet (Box-folder 015:030)
- Vamik Volkan Papers - Georgia Project: Pamphlet of Domestic Violence [Subject: Psycho-Social Portrait of Victims], 2001, Pamphlet (Box-folder 015:031)
- Vamik Volkan Papers - Georgia Project: Volkan's Article on Georgian Movies, N.D., TD (Box-folder 015:032)
- Vamik Volkan Papers - Georgia Project: Pamphlet of GCRT (Georgia Center for Psychosocial and Medical Rehabilitation of Torture Victims) N.D., Pamphlet (Box-folder 015:033)
- Vamik Volkan Papers - Islamic/Western Dialogue: Comments on Conference, 2007(11), TD (Box-folder 015:034)
- Vamik Volkan Papers - PAKH: Volkan's Lecture on "Siblings in the Unconscious", 1997(2/27), Postcard, TD (Box-folder 015:035)
  Lecture Annoucement, Letter
- Vamik Volkan Papers - PAKH: Volkan's Report, "My Experience with PAKH Core Group and Transgenerational Transmission of Trauma", 1998, TD) (Box-folder 015:036)
- Vamik Volkan Papers - PAKH: International Symposium, 1998(8/14-16), Pamphlet (Box-folder 015:037)
- Vamik Volkan Papers - PAKH: Letter from Dr. Bernard Sonntag, 1999(6/15), TD (Box-folder 015:038)
- Vamik Volkan Papers - PAKH: Letter from Johannes Pfafflin, 1999(8/20), TD (Box-folder 015:039)
- Vamik Volkan Papers - PAKH: Letter from Dr. Bernard Sonntag and Johannes Pfafflin, 2006(5/29), TD (Box-folder 015:040)
- Vamik Volkan Papers - CSMHI: Statement concerning the Proposed Division of Psychoanalytic Studies, Department of Behavioral Medicine and Psychiatry, 1980(7/28), TD (Box-folder 016:001)
- Vamik Volkan Papers - CSMHI: Newsletter of the Division of Psychoanalytic Studies, 1983(10), Newsletter (Box-folder 016:002)
- Vamik Volkan Papers - CSMHI: Volkan's Invitation Letter to a Cocktail Party with Eisenhower Exchange Fellows Program Participants from Philippines, 1986(10/12), TD (Box-folder 016:003)
- Vamik Volkan Papers - CSMHI: Volkan's Invitation Letter to a Cocktail Party with Eisenhower Exchange Fellows Program Participants from Korea, 1987(9/25), TD (Box-folder 016:004)
  Invitation Letter, Participants List
- Vamik Volkan Papers - CSMHI: Proposal to the Massey Foundation for the Establishment of the Center for the Study of the Mind and Human Communications, 1987(11/3), TD (Box-folder 016:005)
- Vamik Volkan Papers - CSMHI: Letter from Samuel W. Lewis [Subject: April Meeting at Charlottesville] 1988(3/2), TD (Box-folder 016:006)
- Vamik Volkan Papers - CSMHI: Draft Report and List of Participants of Interdisciplinary Approach to Unofficial Diplomacy Conference, 1988(4/21-24), TD (Box-folder 016:007)
- Vamik Volkan Papers - CSMHI: Letters to Robert M. Carey, 1988(6/2), TD (Box-folder 016:008)
- Vamik Volkan Papers - CSMHI: Letter to the Massey Foundation to the Armand Hammer Foundation, 1988(6/2), TD (Box-folder 016:009)
- Vamik Volkan Papers - CSMHI: Letters to the Massey Foundation, 1988(6/27-8/12), TD (Box-folder 016:010)
- Vamik Volkan Papers - CSMHI: Report on the Establishment of the Center for the Study of Mind and Human Interaction, 1988(10/17), TD (Box-folder 016:011)
- Vamik Volkan Papers - CSMHI: Seminar on Conflict Resolution for the 1989 Eisenhower Exchange Fellowships Program - Irelnad, North & South, 1989(8/9), TD (Box-folder 016:012)
- Vamik Volkan Papers - CSMHI: Letter from Robert M. Carey, 1988(10/20), TD (Box-folder 016:013)
- Vamik Volkan Papers - CSMHI: Building 914 Renovations, 1988-1989, TD (Box-folder 016:014)
  Letter, Report, Purchase Order Forms(Photocopies)
- Vamik Volkan Papers - CSMHI: Letter to William E. Massey of Signal travel Inc., 1989(5/18), TD (Box-folder 016:015)
- Vamik Volkan Papers - CSMHI: Index to Mind and Human Interaction(Vol. 1-5, 1989-1994) 1989-1994, TD (Box-folder 016:016)
- Vamik Volkan Papers - CSMHI: Mind and Human Interaction Issue of June 1990(Vol. 2, No.1), 1990(6), TD (Box-folder 016:017)
- Vamik Volkan Papers - CSMHI: Letter from Virginius Pocius, 1990(6/16), TD (Box-folder 016:018)
- Vamik Volkan Papers - CSMHI: Letter to William E. Massey of Signal travel Inc., 1990(7/5), TD (Box-folder 016:019)
- Vamik Volkan Papers - CSMHI: Letter from Peter M. Benda of Eisenhower Exchange Fellowship, Inc., 1990(9/7), TD (Box-folder 016:020)
- Vamik Volkan Papers - CSMHI: Advisory Board Meeting, 1990(9/24), TD (Box-folder 016:021)
- Vamik Volkan Papers - CSMHI: Letter from Bob Cullen, 1990(9/24), TD (Box-folder 016:022)
- Vamik Volkan Papers - CSMHI: A Brief History, Ongoing Projects, and Associated Scholars, 1990(10), TD (Box-folder 016:023)
- Vamik Volkan Papers - CSMHI: Letter from Donald T. Campbell, 1991(1/3), TD (Box-folder 016:024)
- Vamik Volkan Papers - CSMHI: Dr. Jaime Stubrin's Lecture on "The Psychological Aspects of Political Life in Argentina", 1991(2/8), TD (Box-folder 016:025)
- Vamik Volkan Papers - CSMHI: Letter from Vytautas J. Bieliauskas, 1991(4/14-15), TD (Box-folder 016:026)
- Vamik Volkan Papers - CSMHI: Ethnity and Political Change Conference, 1991(4/18-21), TD (Box-folder 016:027)
- Vamik Volkan Papers - CSMHI: Letter from Harold H. Saunders, 1991(4/21), TD (Box-folder 016:028)
- Vamik Volkan Papers - CSMHI: Letter from World Federation for Mental Health, 1991(4/25), TD (Box-folder 016:029)
- Vamik Volkan Papers - CSMHI: Meeting with the Massey Foundation, 1991(5/16), TD (Box-folder 016:030)
- Vamik Volkan Papers - CSMHI: Letters from 1991(7/3), TD (Box-folder 016:031)
- Vamik Volkan Papers - CSMHI: Letters from Samuel W. Lewis, 1991(7/29), TD (Box-folder 016:032)
- Vamik Volkan Papers - CSMHI: Letters from Anatoly B. Golubovsky, 1991(8/29), TD (Box-folder 016:033)
- Vamik Volkan Papers - CSMHI: Letter to Robert Carey, 1991(9/3), TD (Box-folder 016:034)
- Vamik Volkan Papers - CSMHI: Announcement of a Workshop Series on "The Relationship of Theory to the Clinical Practice of Psychoanalytic Therapy", 1991(9/28)-1992(9/26), TD (Box-folder 016:035)
  Workshop Announcement
- Vamik Volkan Papers - CSMHI: Correspondence with Blema Steinberg, 1991(10/2-11/6), TD (Box-folder 016:036)
- Vamik Volkan Papers - CSMHI: Correspondence from Oleg G. Peressypkin, Ambassador of the USSR, 1991(11/20), TD (Box-folder 016:037)
- Vamik Volkan Papers - CSMHI: Report on Blue Ridge Hospital, 1992, TD (Box-folder 016:038)
- Vamik Volkan Papers - CSMHI Workshop: The Relationship of Theory to Psychoanalytic Theory, 1992(1/8), TD (Box-folder 016:039)
  Memorandum, Workshop Announcement
- Vamik Volkan Papers - CSMHI: Correspondence from Zaur P. Roustam-Zade of the Azerbaijan Republic, 1992(2/20), TD (Box-folder 016:040)